<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Prague Guide</string>


    <!-- Main Attractions -->
    <!-- Prague Castle -->
    <string name="prague_castle_name">Prague Castle</string>
    <string name="prague_castle_address">Address: 119 08 Prague 1</string>
    <string name="prague_castle_description">Prague Castle has been an important symbol of the Czech
        state for more than a thousand years. It was founded in the 9th century and became the seat
        of Czech rulers and later presidents. The castle, one of the largest complexes in the world,
        is made up of historical palaces, offices, church and fortification buildings, gardens and
        picturesque spots. It covers an area of 45 hectares. The panoramic view of Prague Castle is
        one of the most spectacular in the world. </string>

    <!-- Charles Bridge -->
    <string name="charles_bridge_name">Charles Bridge</string>
    <string name="charles_bridge_address">Address: Karlův most, 110 00 Prague 1</string>
    <string name="charles_bridge_description">Charles Bridge is a historic bridge that crosses the
        Vltava river in Prague, Czech Republic. Its construction started in 1357 under the auspices
        of King Charles IV, and finished in the beginning of the 15th century.</string>

    <!-- Old Town -->
    <string name="old_town_name">Old Town</string>
    <string name="old_town_address">Address: Prague 1</string>
    <string name="old_town_description">Old Town, or Staré Mesto, is a lively cobblestoned hub with
        landmark attractions such as the medieval Astronomical Clock and the Gothic Church of Our
        Lady Before Týn, on Old Town Square. The Rudolfinum concert hall hosts classical music,
        while the Estates Theatre stages ballet and opera. Student nightlife is centered around the
        vast 5-story Karlovy Lázně dance club.</string>

    <!-- St. Vitus Cathedral -->
    <string name="vitus_cathedral_name">St. Vitus Cathedral</string>
    <string name="vitus_cathedral_address">Address: III. nádvoří 48/2, 119 01 Prague 1</string>
    <string name="vitus_cathedral_description">Built over a time span of almost 600 years, St Vitus
        is one of the most richly endowed cathedrals in central Europe. It is pivotal to the
        religious and cultural life of the Czech Republic, housing treasures that range from the
        14th-century mosaic of the Last Judgement and the tombs of St Wenceslas and Charles IV, to
        the baroque silver tomb of St John of Nepomuck, the ornate Chapel of St Wenceslas, and art
        nouveau stained glass by Alfons Mucha</string>

    <!-- Clubs -->
    <!-- Karlovy Lazne -->
    <string name="karlovy_lazne_name">Karlovy lázně</string>
    <string name="karlovy_lazne_address">Address: Novotného lávka 198/13, 110 00 Praha-Staré Město</string>
    <string name="karlovy_lazne_description">Karlovy Lazne is the largest facility of its kind in
        Central Europe. Thanks to its five music clubs on five separate floors, it is also one of
        the best technically equipped club’s in the world. The themed floors are one-of-a-kind for
        their original character, which is further enhanced by the historical interior and
        architecture of the building built at the turn of the 15th century, which have been
        preserved. Together with modern facilities and music to suit all tastes certainly creates
        an entirely unique atmosphere, which has made Karlovy Lazne one of the most visited dance
        club’s in the Czech Republic.</string>

    <!-- Roxy -->
    <string name="roxy_name">Roxy Prague</string>
    <string name="roxy_address">Address: Dlouhá 33, 110 00 Staré Město</string>
    <string name="roxy_description">Since its opening in 1992 ROXY has become one of the most
        important places of local dance scene, where many of legendary concerts have taken part.
        You can also visit cafe, gallery and theater NoD which is right above ROXY club.</string>

    <!-- Nebe -->
    <string name="nebe_name">Nebe</string>
    <string name="nebe_address">Address: Václavské nám. 802/56, 110 00 Nové Město</string>
    <string name="nebe_description">Also called Heaven, location is directly on fun-packed Wenceslas
        Square, right in the heart of Prague, making a night out ultra-easy and convenient, as well
        as just plain fun. This Nebe location features an amazing glowing-sphere light fixture set
        with angels, and distinctly Art Deco design all around the stylish bar to ensure that your
        Prague nightlife experience will be so very heavenly, as its name implies.</string>

    <!-- Cross Club -->
    <string name="cross_club_name">Cross Club</string>
    <string name="cross_club_address">Address: Plynární 1096/23, 170 00 Holešovice</string>
    <string name="cross_club_description">The Cross club is a uniquely designed multicultural centre
        which houses a real crossroads of cultures and a variety of styles and genres in the centre
        of Prague Holešovice. For many years, the Cross club has been an integral part of the Prague
        cultural scene, respected not only in the Czech Republic, but also abroad.</string>

    <!-- Parks -->
    <!-- Letna park -->
    <string name="letna_park_name">Letná Park</string>
    <string name="letna_park_address">Address: 7, Praha, Praha 7</string>
    <string name="letna_park_description">This extensive park with grassy areas, mature trees, a
        colorful assortment of bushes planted on the hillsides, and a long plane tree-lined avenue
        provides not only a pleasant to sit and relax, but also unparalleled views of the city,
        especially from the Hanavský Pavilion - a unique cast-iron building with a restaurant.</string>

    <!-- Petrin park -->
    <string name="petrin_park_name">Petřín Park</string>
    <string name="petrin_park_address">Address: Petřínské sady 417/5, 118 00 Praha 1</string>
    <string name="petrin_park_description">Petřín Park is one of the largest urban green areas and
        its slopes are an oasis of calm in the center of Prague. The Rose Garden, or rosarium, at
        the top of Petrin Hill, Nebozízek Garden and the Seminary Garden with more than 2,100 fruit
        trees are particularly magical</string>

    <!-- Vitkov park -->
    <string name="vitkov_name">Park Vítkov</string>
    <string name="vitkov_address">Address: 130 00 Prague 3</string>
    <string name="vitkov_description">The dominant feature of this nearly 3 km-long inline track is
        the well-lit tunnel, which takes you from one side of Vitkov Hill to the other, onto a
        bridge across Koněvova street, on which you can skate all the way to the main train station.</string>

    <!-- Riegrovy sady -->
    <string name="riegrovy_sady_name">Riegrovy Sady</string>
    <string name="riegrovy_sady_address">Address: Riegrovy sady, Praha 2</string>
    <string name="riegrovy_sady_description">Located in the gorgeous Art Nouveau district of
        Vinohrady bordering Zizkov is the lush and rather large Riegrovy Sady (Rieger’s Park). This
        pleasant park stretches between Italská, Chopinova, Polská, and Vozová streets and is one of
        the most popular leisure spots in Prague 2.</string>

    <!-- Bars -->
    <!-- Vzorkovna -->
    <string name="vzorkovna_name">Vzorkovna</string>
    <string name="vzorkovna_address">Address: Národní 339/11, 110 00 Staré Město</string>
    <string name="vzorkovna_description">Vzorkovna is a multi-functional, alternative, and cultural
        hodgepodge – the best of what Prague’s creative people have to offer. Dark nooks and candles
        that leave tracks of time behind. Meeting point for musicians who come to jam with others.
        Unetice beer, wine or tea, everything served in jam jars. A good place to hide.</string>

    <!-- Harley's -->
    <string name="harleys_name">Harley\'s</string>
    <string name="harleys_address">Address: Dlouhá 704/18, 110 00 Staré Město</string>
    <string name="harleys_description">Harley’s Bar is labeled as the ‘coolest Hell on earth’ making
        it definitely an interesting bar to check out while hanging out in the center of gorgeous
        Prague. The hip cellar bar is one of the most popular Prague nighttime hangouts making it
        the place to be on nights out with your friends.</string>

    <!-- Chapeau Rouge -->
    <string name="chapeau_rouge_name">Chapeau Rouge</string>
    <string name="chapeau_rouge_address">Address: Jakubská 2, Praha 1</string>
    <string name="chapeau_rouge_description">In the popular Chapeau Rouge club / bar, open since
        1919, you will find a variety of rooms and levels to match your variety of moods. Chapeau
        Rouge has in fact, three floors, four bars, and three stages. Depending on what you seek,
        Prague's renowned Chapeau Rouge will definitely satisfy. If you happen to be heading to the
        Chapeau for a live show, then you will most definitely not be disappointed.</string>

    <!-- M1 Lounge -->
    <string name="m1_lounge_name">M1 Lounge</string>
    <string name="m1_lounge_address">Address: Masna 1, Praha 1</string>
    <string name="m1_lounge_description">Located in the hip city center of Prague close to the
        gorgeous Old Town Square is the super popular M1 Lounge, one of the best places to be seen
        doing the nightlife rounds in Prague. This stylish and happening place has it all and when
        the sun goes down you can be sure that all the beautiful people in the city flock to M1
        searching for fun, good music to dance to, mischief, strong mouthwatering cocktails, smoking
        shishas and much more.</string>


</resources>
